RAZVAN ROTARU

• DETAILS •

Bucharest Romania (+40) 0761 970 053 razvanrtr@outlook.com

• LINKS •

Portfolio

LinkedIn

° SKILLS °

C

C++

C#

Unity

Unreal

CUDA

Git

Direct3D

OpenGL

Mathematics

Python

Firebase

LANGUAGES

English

German

Romanian

PROFILE

Passionate game developer with technical academic background of over 5 years. Proficient in various platforms and languages. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Bringing forth a positive attitude, critical thinking and a sprinkle of creativity.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

DevOps Engineer Intern at Thales, Bucharest

September 2021 — December 2021

Automated software integration and deployment processes using cloud technologies maintaining transparency with the Senior Software Developers.

Unity Game Developer at Tractor Set Go, Bucharest

March 2022 — June 2022

Implemented various game systems with different mechanics, server functionality for data manipulation and validation and visual components and tools for the Design Team.

Junior Gameplay Programmer at Ubisoft, Bucharest

July 2022 — Present

Developed realistic wildlife AI and game modes in direct collaboration with multiple studios.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science, University Politechnica of Bucharest

October 2015 — July 2020

Master's in Computer Graphics, University Politehnica of Bucharest

October 2020 — Present

★ PROJECTS

Animal Oasis

October 2021 — February 2022

A VR game designed to offer a relaxing experience in a friendly world.

- Simulated a realistic behavior of animals using States and Decision Trees.
- Created animations for the models and designed a few regions.
- · Technologies: Unity, C#, Oculus2, Git

Physics Engine

October 2021 — February 2022

Simulated Physics for different shapes both on CPU and accelearted on GPU.

- Used Separating Axis Theorem (optimized with Gauss Maps) for collision detection and the Sutherland-Hodgman algorithm for clipping.
- Technologies used: Unity, C#, CUDA, Git, SVN

Dodge TH!S

April 2021 — February 2022

A challenging mobile RPG with dynamic mechanics staring a mage and its dog.

- Implemented a complete passive attacking system based on orbiting energy orbs and the abilities to dash and to consume the orbs in order to shoot them.
- Designed the dog companion AI using the State Pattern and Decision Trees.
- Implemented leveling-up system and enemy AI using the Observer Pattern.
- · Technologies used: Unity, C#, SketchFab, Git

Y EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

γ Contributor at StudentHub

February 2021 — February 2022